<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PlayTime on Prefech Documentation</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/</link><description>Recent content in PlayTime on Prefech Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Requirements</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/requirments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/requirments/</guid><description>Requirements FXServer OxMyQL Forum Post GitHub</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/features/</guid><description>Main Features Saves the playtime of every player External acessable info you can use on your website! (SERVER_IP:PORT/Prefech_playTime/info) Export function to get the total play time and current session time in any resource you need it. Export will return a table with the values in seconds.
exports.Prefech_PlayTime:getPlayTime(PLAYER_ID) want to give players access to certain things after being x amount of time online. you - can simpliy check with the export if you have played long enough!</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/commands/</guid><description>Commands Name Example Usage getPlayTime /getPlayTime 12 Will show you the playtime of the target player. (If no target specified it will return your own playtime.)</description></item><item><title>Export</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/export/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/playtime/export/</guid><description>The export will return a table with the player’s session time and the player’s total play time. For example source is the player id and we want to check their time played on the server. We will run the export in our function like this:
local playtime = exports.Prefech_PlayTime:getPlayTime(source) Now the variable playtime will be a table. The table will include both the session and total playtime.
Session time in the table is named Session Total playtime in the table is named Total The table returns the Total and Session playtime in seconds.</description></item></channel></rss>