<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RPChat on Prefech Documentation</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/</link><description>Recent content in RPChat on Prefech Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Requirements</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/requirments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/requirments/</guid><description>Requirements FXServer Make sure to update your chat resource: https://github.com/citizenfx/cfx-server-data/tree/master/resources/%5Bgameplay%5D/chat</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/features/</guid><description>Main Features Basic chat commands /me /ooc /tweet /announce Chat modes (Use Tab to switch between modes.) Staff chat: to give easy and quick access to staff onmly chat ingame. Tweet: to post those tweets even easier. Me: for when you&amp;rsquo;re in that amazing rp secene and you don&amp;rsquo;t want to keep typing /me Export to make custom messages to chat.</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/commands/</guid><description>Commands Name Example Usage ooc /ooc This is out of Character Will post a OOC message in chat. tweet /tweet This is how you post a tweet Will post a Twitter message in chat. me /me Stashing the goodies Will post a Action message in proximity chat. announce /announce My cool announcement Will post a Announcement message in chat.</description></item><item><title>Export</title><link>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/export/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.prefech.com/rpchat/export/</guid><description>The export will return a table with the player’s session time and the player’s total play time. For example source is the player id and we want to check their time played on the server. We will run the export in our function like this:
local playtime = exports.Prefech_PlayTime:getPlayTime(source) Now the variable playtime will be a table. The table will include both the session and total playtime.
Session time in the table is named Session Total playtime in the table is named Total The table returns the Total and Session playtime in seconds.</description></item></channel></rss>